SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
10 MONTHS LATER
Shang Zhitao.
You haven't contacted me
for almost a week.
I told you
that I was conducting a study
in the Gobi Desert with the project team.
The signal over there was bad.
Aren't you going to the US
to report your work?
You haven't left yet?
You're so heartless.
Do you think I can leave
without making sure you're fine?
It's still a long-distance relationship.
Where I'm at makes no difference.
The US and Beijing are the same.
Luan Nian.
I wish you success in your report.
When I'm back home,
let's have a video call.
I want to see Luke.
Say it again.
You just want to see Luke?
Of course.
That's my dog.
Say it again.
Whose dog?
Our dog.
Let's leave it here. I'll arrive soon.
I WILL WATCH OVER YOU FROM BEYOND
THIS WORLD, UNTIL YOUR LIFE IS WHOLE
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Tao.
Why are you here?
My assignment in Northwestern China
is ending.
I wanted to see you before I leave.
Why didn't you send me a text?
What if you didn't see me?
I just came back from a business trip.
Come up. Let's have a drink.
It's fine. It's quite late.
I have to hurry and catch the last bus.
This is for you.
I got it from the mountains.
I think you might like it.
There was a year
when I received flowers
every day for a week at work.
Was that you?
Back then, you said
you wanted flowers so much,
but if it was prepared beforehand,
it wouldn't be surprising.
So, I sent them for a few days as a prank.
I hope you liked them back then.
Thanks, Zhu.
I liked them a lot.
Oh, my work here is done
after a month.
When I return to Beijing,
let's go watch a movie, okay?
Midnight screening.
We'll go every weekend.
Let's watch all the old movies together.
We'll call Sun Yu too.
Sure.
I'll buy the tickets.
No. Let Sun Yu buy them.
Her team is doing very well now.
You haven't seen each other for so long.
If Sun Yu knows that you're going back,
she will be so happy.
- Let me tell Sun Yu.
- Don't.
Don't disturb her.
Before you
return to Beijing, do you need
to go back to your hometown?
How's your mother?
Is she doing well?
She passed away.
When did that happen?
During the Chinese New Year.
You…
Why didn't you tell us?
That was the time when all of you
were reunited with your family members.
I didn't want all of you to be sad.
What about your younger sister?
Is she well?
She is studying well.
What about your father?
He's doing well too.
What about you?
Are you well, Sun Yuanzhu?
I'm well.
That's good enough.
Let me take you to the bus stop.
I'll drop off my luggage.
Wait for me.
Tao.
Actually, I'm unwell.
I'm very sad.
I've put in a lot of effort.
I tried to change.
But no matter what I do,
and how much effort I put into it,
I couldn't achieve the result I wanted.
I've put in 99% effort into it.
Why can't I…
get that final 1%
luck?
Don't cry.
It's fine.
Don't cry, all right?
You will get that 1%.
Sun Yu.
Sun Yuanzhu's mother passed away.
He is quite sad. Do you want to visit him?
I'll come tomorrow.
Let me send you the address.
No need.
I've been there many times.
Throughout my whole life,
I've only traveled a long way,
regardless of any obstacles,
again and again for his sake.
Just to have a meal with him
and have a quick chat.
Then,
I'd take the early flight back
the next day.
I'll be there tomorrow.
Okay.
BEIJING TO LANZHOU
FLIGHT TICKET PURCHASE WEBSITE
SELECT PASSENGER: SUN YU
TOTAL: RMB 734, PAY NOW
PAYMENT SUCCESSFUL
SHANG ZHITAO
The number you are calling is busy.
Hello?
Luan Nian.
Are you busy?
Right.
I was busy.
Then, I'll video call you tomorrow.
All right?
I'm going to the US
the day after tomorrow.
I'll leave Luke at the pet shop.
I'm returning to Beijing next week.
Okay.
I'm hanging up.
GROUP CHAT: WAS TRACY TALKING ABOUT YOU
AT THE MEETING?
Is she going to be our future lady boss?
In the future, we must be cautious
when we speak in front of Yilia and Luke.
I also heard from our US colleagues
that they go on
this business trip together.
They also have meals together often.
Yilia is a woman born in a rich family.
She's a good match for Luke.
I heard Yilia is the daughter of Mr. You,
our biggest client.
Her father likes Luke a lot.
He's going to allocate
next year's advertising budget to Lime.
Tao.
Lumi misses you so much.
Shang Zhitao!
You're finally back!
I miss you so much.
Are you staying for good this time?
Next month. I'm coming back
for good next month.
Do you know what kind of life
I was living in Lime
while you were assigned to work abroad?
I've not met another coworker like you
who is impressive,
intelligent, and amazing after you left.
Stop praising me.
Without you, who's going to pamper me?
Let me tell you.
You'll soon be promoted
to specialist in Lime.
You might be the one
pampering me in the future.
I'm still preparing my work report.
Let's wait
until the assessment result is out.
I've gone through everything for you.
The judges of the first round
are the bosses of each division
and two former specialists.
Will is mine.
If he dares give you a low score,
I'll not forgive him.
Tracy has been treating you well, right?
I don't have to say
anything more about Luke.
He's fair, just, and open.
So, your promotion to a specialist
is set in stone.
Is Will
yours?
Well, soon.
Soon? I thought he was already yours.
You're so bad. Are you teasing me?
Of course not. I'll buy you coffee later.
That's more like it.
Luke is back. Do you know that?
Isn't Luke staying in the US for a month?
He came back early.
Go and report to him
when he is here later.
Specialist.
Luke.
Come in.
You're back.
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
I made a last-minute change to my plans.
What is it?
No…
It's nothing.
I just came to report to you.
Sure.
Why are you still here?
I'm waiting for you.
What's wrong?
Something bad happened
when you were in the US?
Everything was normal.
We've not seen each other for two months.
Don't you miss me?
I missed you a lot.
Is that so?
I didn't.
What's wrong?
Did I offend you somehow?
You're scaring me.
Me? Scaring you? No way.
You insisted on staying
in Northwestern China.
You said you liked it there.
What's the point of missing you?
I can't transfer you back either.
You have your own definition of success
and your own way of living.
I respect that.
I have no right to interfere.
You have the right
to choose your own life.
No problem.
Can we talk nicely?
What are you trying to say here?
What am I trying to say?
My girlfriend was talking
with another man downstairs
while crying and hugging him
the whole night.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by
hugging and crying with someone else?
Shang Zhitao, you're quite something.
You keep saying you miss me,
but you keep looking for your next one.
Do you think you are so charming
that you can start fooling around
- with different men?
- Luan Nian.
You can choose not to trust me,
but you cannot accuse me
of something I never did.
Did I confront you about this?
Did I confront you
when you dined with another woman?
I didn't, right?
Did I confront you
about why the company
is full of rumors about you two?
I didn't, right? Because I trust you.
I've always thought that
we knew each other well
in terms of our social circle.
However, you are pinning
such a big accusation on me
because I went to comfort my friend.
Should we just avoid any interactions
with the other gender
because we are together?
No need. I didn't avoid it.
I can also get along well
with women whom I admire
and work well with me.
Even if I get off work,
I don't think
having a meal or having a chat
is a waste of time.
I know.
I know you can admire
someone you admire openly.
I've never felt jealous about it.
It's true.
So, Luan Nian, please view
my relationship
with Sun Yuanzhu rationally.
After all, during a few difficult moments
in my life,
it was him,
Lumi, and Sun Yu who kept me company.
Luan Nian, I want you to know
that no matter how much I love you,
I'd never give up my friends.
I also won't interfere with you
working with Song Ying.
That's a fair exchange.
I hope you remember and stick to it.
Were you at Northwestern China that day?
How come you knew Sun Yuanzhu cried?
I would like to know
why you came that day.
I would like to know why you cried.
Sun Yuanzhu's family member passed away.
He was sad.
He seemed off emotionally.
I figured he was ill. He couldn't eat.
I cried because I felt bad.
Luan Nian. He is
a really good friend of mine.
Can you not get the wrong idea about him
and about our friendship?
I'll try my best.
So, you were there that day.
Why?
Because I suddenly missed you.
TIANTONG YUAN STATION TIMETABLE
REDEFINING THE ROLE OF THE ACCOUNT MANAGER
FROM EXECUTION TO SOLUTIONS
2016-2017: METHODOLOGY CONSOLIDATION
AND STRATEGIC ELEVATION
WORK PERFORMANCE REPORT
1. BRING PARENTS TO TRAVEL
2. LEARN ENGLISH 3. LEARN HOW TO DRIVE
4. LEARN FRENCH 5. GO TO TIBET
6. TRAVEL ABROAD
7. READ 200 BOOKS
8. MAKE THREE FRIENDS AND ABOVE
9. MARRY THE PERSON I LOVE
10. BECOME A LIME SPECIALIST
Flora.
If you are ready, let's begin.
I joined Lime in 2012.
My first lesson about work
was from my interview with my boss.
I had to shed my student's mindset,
get my superior's attention,
and manage upward.
Time is precious for everyone at work,
including mine.
Are you done?
I thought your time was worthless,
so I can put off your task.
I understand.
In the future,
I'll make my request directly.
Thank you for your guidance.
My first project at Lime
was an e-commerce advertisement.
This project taught me
to be clear about the scope
of my responsibilities.
Due to a messy report given to the client,
I was scolded by my superior
and felt aggrieved.
Now, I get it.
Being a professional
is not about completing the task,
but completing it correctly.
In my third year in Lime,
I started digging deeply
into industry data
and analyzing
the company's past case reports.
I stepped into our clients' shoes
to think about what they need,
what they care about,
what I can provide to them,
and my individual strength.
Until I completed an S-class project
on my own,
I finally understood
the meaning of being an account manager.
Until now,
I still remember the time I first met you.
It has been six years now.
Time passes so quickly.
Before the other two judges
ask you questions,
I'd like to thank you
for your contribution
over the last six years
on behalf of the company.
Thank you, Flora.
How was it?
I did my best.
When will the result be out?
Probably during the annual meeting.
Then, let me congratulate you
on becoming a Lime Specialist in advance.
Let's pick up Yuanzhu later,
and we'll go grocery shopping.
I must tell Zhu
that I completed the work report
using the method he taught me.
I must thank him well.
His residential study ends today.
I previously coaxed him
into doing a check-up
with me at the hospital.
He does have depression.
However, he is willing to accept treatment
and take medications.
The treatment is quite effective.
He has been eating well,
and he started smiling.
He loves to talk too.
A few days ago,
I took him to watch a movie at night.
He was having fun.
He was so happy
that I didn't know what to say.
When I saw him smiling,
I felt happy too.
Me too.
When I see both of you happy,
I feel happy too.
Our lives
will surely get better.
Yes.
Look.
It's so pretty.
Hurry.
Take a picture with your phone.
Send it to Yuanzhu.
Tell him to wait for us.
Why isn't he picking up?
He's not picking up?
- Let me call him.
- He didn't reply to my text either.
Call him.
THE CROWNING MASTERPIECE
ON CHANG'AN AVENUE
Are you calling him?
Yes. He's not answering.
He didn't answer?
Is he working overtime without telling me?
I don't think so.
He would have told us beforehand.
Let me send him another text.
A colleague of mine committed suicide.
It just happened.
He was fine.
Why did he commit suicide?
‪What's so hard for him to get over?
This place, right?
It was split open. His head was…
I heard he was developing
self-driving cars.
- He jumped down from upstairs.
- That floor.
From upstairs.
- It's so tall.
- I wonder what happened to him.
I heard the fall was really bad.
Captain, the victim's phone is ringing.
Hello?
Are you the victim's family member?
Officer. Who is this?
An employee of this building.
I can't disclose anything else.
An employee?
I really want to jump into the clouds.
Actually, I'm unwell.
I'm very sad.
But no matter what I did,
and how much effort I put into it,
I couldn't achieve the result I wanted.
I've put in 99% effort into it.
Why can't I get that final 1%
luck?
No.
It's not him, right?
It's not real, Tao.
Everyone, don't gather here.
Disperse. Move along.
Take care of the body first.
Contact the coroner
and his family members.
EMERGENCY RESCUE
You must be hungry.
I am Sun Yuanzhu.
WELCOME HOME
Does your name mean
"With fierce ambition
that reaches beyond the four seas,
I spread my wings
and long to soar to distant horizons?"
I bought many ingredients today.
It's so heavy.
I also bought flour.
Let me make handmade noodles
for all of you later.
I want to get a longer dining table
so everyone can sit and work together.
Then, I want to rearrange the living room.
The sofa and bookshelves are new.
This is Luke's home now.
Tomato and egg noodles without tomatoes
have no souls.
Have a spoonful.
Have two spoonfuls.
Add this yourself.
- Try it.
- You too.
Try it first.
Delicious.
Have another spoonful.
Sun Yu.
Sun Yu, stop.
It tastes like Yuanzhu's cooking.
THOUGHTS FROM THE CUTE YUANZHU
I'm going to be late.
Don't need to send me off. I can go alone.
Will we…
have a bright future ahead of us?
Will I ever get to see the future
where we
love each other
and spend many years
walking through life together?
Sorry.
Sun Yu.
I will watch you fall in love,
get married, have kids,
be happy forever,
and never suffer from beyond the world.
SUN YU: I WILL WATCH YOU FALL IN LOVE
GET MARRIED, HAVE KIDS
BE HAPPY FOREVER
AND NEVER SUFFER FROM BEYOND THE WORLD
Sun Yuanzhu,
I hope I can meet you
when I'm 17 years old in my next life.
I want to give all my love
to you.
From when I'm young
until I grow old,
I hope
all the "I love yous" I told you
will become the lights on your journey
that illuminate your path
to the afterlife.
I hope
you no longer suffer.
Come in.
Do you want some water?
Yuanzhu's diary.
Keep it. It's a keepsake.
Read it first.
He mentioned you.
Her name is Shang Zhitao.
Like the flourishing peach tree
with its brilliant blossoms,
the name perfectly suits her.
Her bright smile
can light up the whole world.
Tao said
she wanted to receive roses.
Sun Yu,
can you give me a bouquet of flowers?
I gave her flowers for a few days,
and I saw how happy she was.
I hope she can be this happy forever.
Tao wrote these words
on the postcard she sent me from Phuket.
I hope smiles are the only thing
you see in your eyes.
TO SUN YUANZHU
MAY YOUR EYES SEE ONLY SMILES
I want to tell her that I hope
every dream she has
won't be an empty dream.
She is like a shining star.
Pure, wonderful,
and out of reach.
I'm like the fox
who watches over her.
I can only look at her from afar
without approaching her.
I can't have her.
I hope Tao will never know about this.
I hope…
I HOPE SHE CAN BE HAPPY FOREVER
…she can do whatever she wants.
I HOPE SHE CAN DO WHATEVER SHE WANTS
Sometimes, staying away
is also a kind of love.
People were born to be free,
but they are always bound by shackles.
Tao doesn't seem happy
in her relationship.
Perhaps
every relationship is just a hierarchy
until you can stand
on equal footing with one another.
I blame myself.
If I had worked harder
and not had so much burden,
could I bring her happiness?
But perhaps being happy is difficult.
I haven't learned it myself.
April is the most miserable month.
Only faded memories remain
on this barren wasteland.
I'm someone who's empty inside,
wandering in the void.
My heart
has also turned into an empty wasteland.
Mom…
passed away.
I yearn for the rain.
I yearn to be nourished.
I yearn…
to be reborn.
But…
is there still hope?
THAT LIGHT, IT SEEMS UNREACHABLE
Farewell,
the world I loved
and the people I loved.
Let's not see each other again.
So you've always known.
Sun Yu.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
I was just
loving him
purely.
It doesn't matter who he liked.
Throughout my long years,
he has given me countless moments
of warmth and kindness.
I, Sun Yu, fell in love with an angel.
He
was an angel.
Why are you crying?
I still remember the time
I first met you.
It has been six years now.
Time passes so quickly.